(Raj:)Why are you
holding hands?
(Raj:)I forbid you to hold hands.
(Priya:)Rajesh, you know Leonard and I
spent the night together.
(Raj:)Yeah, but you were just
sleeping,
(Raj:)because I forboded you
to have sex.
The word is "forbade""
(Raj:)You sure?
That doesn't sound right.
(Priya:)Listen, Rajesh, Leonard and I
have decided
(Priya:)to see each other again,
(Priya:)and you don't get
to tell me
(Priya:)who I can and can't have
a relationship with.
(Sheldon:)Actually, he can.
(Sheldon:)The Hindu Code of Manu is
very clear in these matters.
(Sheldon:)If a woman's father is
not around,
(Sheldon:)the duty of controlling her base
desires falls
(Sheldon:)to the closest male member of
her family, in this case, Raj.
(Sheldon:)The code also states
(Sheldon:)that if she disobeys,
she will be reborn
"in the womb of a jackal
and tormented by diseases."
(Sheldon:)If true,
(Sheldon:)that seems
like an awfully large gamble
(Sheldon:)given that the prize is Leonard.